tohappytravel.com 2009-03-06

# Privacy Policy - tohappytravel.com

**tohappytravel.com** sees great importance in protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to explain the manner in which tohappytravel.com collects, uses, and discloses the personal information provided by you as a result of the use of tohappytravel.com's Web Site and the content, information and services provided through the Web Site by tohappytravel.com.

**Users' Consent.** BY ACCESSING THIS WEB SITE, THE WEB SITE LOCATED AT THE URL WWW.tohappytravel.com AND/OR ANY OTHER SITE PROVIDED BY tohappytravel.com (COLLECTIVELY, THE "SITE"), YOU ARE SIGNIFYING, EXPRESSING AND PROVIDING YOUR CONSENT TO THE INFORMATION COLLECTION, INFORMATION USAGE, AND OTHER PROCEDURES DESCRIBED IN THE PRIVACY POLICY BELOW. tohappytravel.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time, without notice, by posting a new privacy policy at this location. The collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by tohappytravel.com will be governed by the version of this Policy in effect at that time. Please check this page periodically for any changes.

**Collection and Use of Information.** In order for you to access certain materials or pages (i.e. author signup, tell a friend, and the like) to register as a user on this Site, this Site requires that you provide certain personal information, including, but not limited to, your name, phone number and e-mail address. We use this information in order to contact you to provide you with further information about our company and services, as well as for other commercial and/or internal purposes such as market research in order to better understand the demographics of our Site visitors and potential customers and partners. We may share this information with our authorized partners and/or with third parties who act for or on behalf of us, but we do not otherwise provide or sell any information gathered on this Site to outside vendors.

**User Tracking.** This Site implements a user tracking feature, whereby the activities of each unique visitor to the Site are monitored. This is done regardless of whether the visitor has registered on the Site or is visiting the Site anonymously, but if you do not register on this Site or fill in your personal details on any forms, you do remain anonymous and we do not discover your identity. If you do register on this Site, our use of user tracking enables us to identify your future and prior activity on the Site, including your activity before you registered. This includes pages on our Site that you visited. User tracking also allows us to determine through which means you have reached our Site (i.e. which search engines or links) up to one web page back. The purpose of our user tracking is to analyze our visitors' actions in order to improve the user experience of visitors to our Site, as well as to better understand the priorities and interests of our potential customers and partners in order to better suit their needs and increase the efficiency of our sales and marketing processes.

**Use of Cookies.** A "cookie" is a small text file transferred by a Web Site to a computer that is browsing the Web Site. Even if you do not register on this Site, upon your first visit to this Site (or subsequent visits if you delete the cookie), a cookie is stored on your computer, which automatically identifies you to the Site. This is done several technical reasons, including enabling the "User Tracking" described above. In addition, for your convenience, the cookie can "autofill" information on forms on the Site, precluding the need for you to fill out the same information on our registration forms each time you want to access information that requires registration. However, cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user; the only personal information we learn about you is that which you provide to us, as described above If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can change the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. In addition, you can delete any cookies that have already been placed on your computer.

**Internet Protocol Addresses.** We collect the IP addresses of all visitors to our Site. We use your IP address in order to administer the Site, help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and for the "User Tracking" described above.  
Hyperlinks. This Site contains hyperlinks to other web sites. This privacy policy applies only to this Site and not to any other sites, including sites accessed by hyperlink from this Site. tohappytravel.com has no responsibility, liability for, or control over those other web sites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, nor has it any control over, the privacy policies of any of these sites. When you leave our Site, including by linking from the Site to another site, you should read the privacy policy, if any, provided by such site.

The applicable law and exclusive jurisdiction for settling any disputes in connection with the use of the Site shall be the laws and jurisdiction of the state of Israel according to the provisions of the then policy in effect.

**tohappytravel.com** will accumulate and process your personal information in the USA, Israel or, from time to time, in other locations at it's discretion in order to provide you with competent and effective service. 

**In order** to assist in protecting the confidentiality of your personal information, tohappytravel.com applies security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, in light of the nature of Internet technologies, security and privacy risks cannot be eliminated and, therefore, tohappytravel.com cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy.

If you have questions please send an e-mail to: [support@tohappytravel.com](mailto:support@tohappytravel.com)
